<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.4 November 13, 2013</version>
  <date>Fri May 30 21:38:23 PDT 2014</date>
  <user>jakrigel</user>
  <sip_name>31</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>147</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>147</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2014WW22</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>1p0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>v3</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>ALL_2014WW22_R1p0_v3</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jakrigel</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist>iah_chandler@intel.com,eig_proj_all@intel.com</sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed></sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
      <sip_customer>20</sip_customer>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>640</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<h2>RTL Updates:</h2>
   <dl>
      <dt>Micro-architecture Updates:</dt>
      <dd>Removed reset on data path in the asynchronous fifo. Adds a flop to keep the same behavior</dd>
      <dd>Asynchronous FIFO now uses a parameter to set all the reset values of idle properly. This should fix some late agents that were having issues with the ISM coming out of IDLE for no reason.</dd>
      <dt>agent_clk now has a gated version to help agents that did not locally clock gate the agent_clk get better clock gating efficiency. Update is not all encumpassing. It is still suggested agents follw the integration guide for clock gating agent_clk.</dt>
      <dt>side_clk going to the asyncfifo now uses gated_side_clk to increase clock gating efficiency in side_clk domain</dt>
      <dt>side_clk going to the idlecnt synchronizer using gated_side_clk to give slightly better clock gating efficiency</dt>
      <dt>PCRS: <dt>
      <dd>PCR <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=12041626">12041626</a>: Migrated to new CTECH Methodology.</dd>
      <dd>PCR <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=12042104">12042104</a>: Unique Extended Headers added in-place of legacy extended header support.</dd>
      <dd>PCR <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=1201316737">1201316737</a>: Universal Synchronizer circuit updated to have an egress counter for each direction.</dd>
      <dt>BUGS: <dt>
      <dd>HSD <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=11015899156">11015899156</a>: Updated assertion that was going off in endpoints that was intended for the routers.</dd>
      <dd>HSD <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=11018138555">11018138555</a>: Universal synchronizer updated to use DEN instead of a manually inserted clock gate. Synthesis should insert clock gates as necessary.</dd>
   </dl>
   
   <h2>Backend Updates:</h2>
   <dl>
      <dt>General Updates: </dt>
      <dd>All tools moved to get RTL lists from ACE. CTECH library gets pulled in automatically this way.</dd>
   </dl>
   
   <h2>Validation Updates:</h2>    ]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
    <sip_specin>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<ul>
      <li>For support file an <b>HSD</b> at <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360">https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360</a></li>
      <li>Please note that Sideband Endpoint instantiations need to be uniquified in all IP's per the SEG POR instantiation and uniquification methodology to avoid module collisions with other instances of the endpoint with other IPs.</li>
      <li>Please read integration guide carefully for handling current clock request logic</li>
      <li>Please read integration guide carefully for conditions of locally clock gating the agent_clk in asynchronous endpoints.</li>
</ul>    ]]>    </sip_specin>
  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
