<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.4 November 13, 2013</version>
  <date>Thu Feb  3 11:33:47 PST 2017</date>
  <user>jignasap</user>
  <sip_name>31</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>147</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>147</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2017WW05</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>1p0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>PICr18</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>ALL_2017WW05_R1p0_PICr18</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jignasap</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist></sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed></sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>0</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
      <h2>RTL Updates:</h2>
      <dl>
         <dt>HSDs: <dt>
         <dd>
            1. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405520412/main">1405520412: "Library name has to be uniquified - iosf_sbc_ep_rtl_lib"</a>:The Base Endpoint RTL can now be uniquified using the "uniquifying" script that is delivered along with the IP. The executable resides in the script folder within the IP_ROOT and requires a "liblist" file (also available in the scripts area). "Uniquifyme" (within the delivered script) changes all the RTL and only certain ACE files/libraries to be prepended with the desired prefix. The remaining TB and ACE UDF/ACERC files are post-edited by the script. So to rerun uniquifcation, undo all the previous changes and redo the steps again (only for EP). Refer Integration guide for the steps.
         </dd>
         <dd>                       
            2.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1504389202/main">1504389202: "IOSF_Sideband_Endpoint_ALL_2016WW50_R1p0_PICr17] Reset pin of i_sync_jta_clkgate_ovrd_agent is connected to async reset without synchronization "</a>:Connected the synchronized reset pin to the synchronizer on a static signal (jta_clkgate_ovrd_agent).       
         </dd>
         <dd>
            3.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1504389204/main">1504389204: "IOSF SB Endpoint] Lintra violation 60024a seen on iosf sb endpoint "</a>:Added the SOC lintra config to the simbuild Lintra flow and fixed the violations on iosf_sb_endpoint. These are new rules that had to be waived.
          </dd>
         <dd>
            4.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1304746990/main">1304746990: "FWD ICL-A0 Emulation + UPF compilation +UC1.0 is failing due to UPF code is reffered to SVA logic"</a>:Added an environment parameter EP_EMULATION_UPF that wraps certain assignments in the upf file. The default value of the parameter is 0. This parameter can be set/unset through the environment and consumers  now use the UPF code, referred in SVA logic in the endpoint, in emulation.                       
         </dd>
         <dd>                         
            5.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405328944/main">1405328944: "TFM: SBE EIG 1639 Tool-lock and CTECH"</a>:Endpoint is aligned to the HDK 1639 tool lock             
         </dd>
         <dd>                         
            5. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405612922/main">1405612922: "Sideband Endpoint visa signal names to be renamed correctly"</a>:This is a signal naming reassignment issue. That doesnot involve any logic additions the assignments of the signals to the VISA bus had to be rearranged to match the descriptions in the visa package. 
        </dd>
        <dd>                         
            6. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405441753/main">1405441753: "FWD (PCR) Enable LintraSVTB SBE"</a>:SVTB Lintra is now enabled on sideband endpoint. The executable can be found along with the other tools supported by sideband.
        </dd>
<dd>                         
            7. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1209205616/main">1209205616: "FWD IOSF_SB_EP not Providing QCDC HDM models (new TFM flow)"
</a>:Sideband Endpoint in HDK runs in the HDM mode. Customers will have to source the endpoint in hdk environment and launch the CDC executables that generate the HDM models.
        </dd>

      </dl>      
      <h2>Backend Updates:</h2>
         <dt> General updates.</dt>
      <h2>Validation Updates:</h2>
         <dt> General updates.</dt>]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
    <sip_knissue>
<![CDATA[
HTML
        <dt> None. </dt>]]>    </sip_knissue>
  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
    <sip_speccon>
<![CDATA[
HTML
 <h2>Integration Notes:</h2>
    <dt>NOTE: The first Sideband Fabric  release with support for parity pins is IOSF_Sideband_Fabric_Compiler_ALL_2014WW38_R1p0_v5</dt> ]]>    </sip_speccon>
  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
    <sip_specin>
<![CDATA[
HTML
 <ul>
         <li>This SBE release uses the "IOSF_SVC_2017WW05"  version of SVC in IRR</li>
         <li>For support file an <b>HSD</b> at <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360">https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360</a></li>
         <li>Please note that Sideband Endpoint instantiations need to be uniquified in all IP's per the SEG POR instantiation and uniquification methodology to avoid module collisions with other instances of the endpoint with other IPs.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for handling current clock request logic</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for conditions of locally clock gating the agent_clk in asynchronous endpoints.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for any necessary power gating logic that may be needed.</li>
         <li>The Zircon scores are uploaded to the IPDS dashboard for the SBE IP at <a href="https://zircon.fm.intel.com/zircon/zircon/zirconReleaseDashboardTable.php?top_filter_checkbox=0&Proj_id=12686&IP_id=17324&milestone_filter=4&Ver_id=all&App_id=1&showlatest=0">https://zircon.fm.intel.com/zircon/zircon/zirconReleaseDashboardTable.php?top_filter_checkbox=0&Proj_id=12686&IP_id=17324&milestone_filter=4&Ver_id=all&App_id=1&showlatest=0</a></li>
      </ul>]]>    </sip_specin>
  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
