<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.4 November 13, 2013</version>
  <date>Fri May 26 14:01:38 PDT 2017</date>
  <user>jignasap</user>
  <sip_name>31</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>147</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>147</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2017WW21</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>1p0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>PICr20</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>ALL_2017WW21_R1p0_PICr20</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jignasap</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist></sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed></sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>1921</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<h2>RTL Updates:</h2>
      <dl>
         <dt>HSDs: <dt>
         <dd>
            1. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405791475/main">1405791475: " Lintra errors/warnings in RP genram module "</a>: The RP genram module (enabled by the RP_ENABLE parameter) is now clean from all lintra warnings. Additional waivers had to be added for this change. The changes are restricted to the RP genram modules (and lintra waiver collaterals).
         </dd>
         <dd>                   
            2.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405821650/main">1405821650: " FWD (PCR) All delivered IP should use CTECH 2.0(lib exportchange)-Endpoint "</a>: Endpoint is fixed to import and consume the CTECH2.0 collaterals using the suggested  ACE BKM. The changes are in the ace files (hdl.udf and cfg/ctech files). Customers can no longer use the previous CTECH1.0 methodology as this change is not backward compatible. This was a known fallout from this change and is recommended and approved change from the PEG IP quality WG. The HSD describes the correct usage (with attached slides) and the changes required to support this TFM update.       
         </dd>
         <dd>
            3.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405900623/main">1405900623: " Synthesis Lint Warning in IOSF sideband endpoint "</a>: New synthesis lint tool used by few customers saw errors in unconnected pins. There are not used by the endpoint and should not be synthesized. This is cleaned up to mitigate customer inconveniences.
          </dd>
         <dd>
            4.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405680984/main">1405680984: " FWD (PCR) Convert iosf sb endpoint parameter "GLOBAL_EP" to a strap to make HIPs spec compliant without physical respin "</a>: There was a request to make the hierarchical header for transparent bridge endpoints, strap based instead of the existing parametric control. This is enabled in the current endpoint together with the parameter so customers can choose either, depending on their requirement. A new parameter and a new input pin is added to support this. Please refer to the Endpoint integration guide for more details.                       
         </dd>
         <dd>                         
            5.  <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405738022/main">1405738022:" FWD IOSF SB EP: CLAIM_DELAY parameter off by 1 "</a>: Endpoint with the variable claim delay feature had this offset in the parameter because of an RTL assumption. This is fixed in the current release. Customers who do not enable the variable claim delay feature in the endpoint, are not affected by this change.              
         </dd>
         <dd>                         
            6. <a
            href="https://hsdes.intel.com/appstore/article/#/1405821683/main">1405821683:" FWD (PCR) Request to recode RTL to work around Xprop/VCSMX tool limitation (originally filed by the misleading title Potential fatal initialization issue due to VCSMX bug) "</a>: An additional paranoia xprop check for indirect indexes is fixed in this endpoint drop.  
         </dd>
         
      </dl>      
      <h2>Backend Updates:</h2>
         <dt> General updates.</dt>
      <h2>Validation Updates:</h2>
         <dt> General updates.</dt>]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
    <sip_knissue>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<dt> None. </dt>]]>    </sip_knissue>
  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
    <sip_speccon>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<h2>Integration Notes:</h2>
    <dt>NOTE: The first Sideband Fabric  release with support for parity pins is IOSF_Sideband_Fabric_Compiler_ALL_2014WW38_R1p0_v5</dt> ]]>    </sip_speccon>
  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
    <sip_specin>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<ul>
         <li>This SBE release is compliant with HDK 1713 tool lock</li>
         <li>This SBE release uses the "IOSF_SVC_2017WW21"  version of SVC in IRR</li>
         <li>For support file an <b>HSD</b> at <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360">https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360</a></li>
         <li>Please note that Sideband Endpoint instantiations need to be uniquified in all IP's per the SEG POR instantiation and uniquification methodology to avoid module collisions with other instances of the endpoint with other IPs.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for handling current clock request logic</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for conditions of locally clock gating the agent_clk in asynchronous endpoints.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for any necessary power gating logic that may be needed.</li>
         <li>The Zircon scores are uploaded to the IPDS dashboard for the SBE
         IP at <a
         href="https://zircon.echo.intel.com/zircon/zirconIPDashboardTable.php?top_filter_checkbox=0&Proj_id=all&IP_id=17324&milestone_filter=all&Ver_id=all&App_id=all&showlatest=0">Zircon
         Score for IOSF Sideband Endpoint</a></li>
      </ul>]]>    </sip_specin>
  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
