<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.4 November 13, 2013</version>
  <date>Mon Mar 10 19:08:17 PDT 2014</date>
  <user>jakrigel</user>
  <sip_name>138</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>528</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>528</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2014WW11</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>1p0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>v3</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>ALL_2014WW11_R1p0_v3</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jakrigel</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist>csg_sip_all@intel.com,csg_sip_proj_all@intel.com</sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed></sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
      <sip_customer>20</sip_customer>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>0</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
   <h2>RTL Updates:</h2>
   <dl>
      <dt>RTL Logic Changes: </dt>
      <dd>Updated sbcinqueue to used a new function called sbc_indexed_value instead of sbc_logb2 to give more accurate number of required bits.</dd>
      <dt>RTL Assertions Updates: </dt>
      <dd>Added an assertion to sbcasyncclkreq to detect any lost wake requests. Will need to look into adding idle assertions too in the future.</dd>
      <dt>RTL Bug Fix: </dt>
      <dd>1018236463: fabric clock request logic now factors in the asynchronous port FIFOs ensuring that the clock will be requested to transfer data between the two clock domains.</dd>
      <dd>1014954027: logic on reset results from caliber showed paths with glitchy logic. The clock request logic has been reviewed to ensure there is no longer glitches or the clock request lines. The clock request module has been modified to prevent glitching caused by the deassertion of wake and assertion of clkgated.
      <dd>1017736408: NP fencing was broken for ingress queue sizes greater than the original maximum of 7. The counters that were overflowing will now self adjust according to the PC ingress queue depth.</dd>
      <dt>PCRS: <dt>
      <dd>58303: DNV emulation related changes made to iosf_sbc_rtr.hdl. emulation_top.sv added to &lt;ip_root&gt;/verif/tb_top/&lt;network&gt;/emulation_top.sv</dd>
   </dl>

   <h2>Dynamo/Collage Updates:</h2>
   <dl>
      <dt>General Updates: </dt>
      <dd>1017830793: Customer environment was using a different version of dot instead of out of the central Intel binary directory. Explicitely asking for Intel version now.</dd>
   </dl>

   <h2>Backend Updates:</h2>
   <dl>
      <dt>General Updates: </dt>
      <dd>Fixed it so that the backend script generator now lets a fabric router have all asynchronous ports.</dd>
      <dd>When running ACE the environment variable CTECH_LIB_NAME must be set to match the CTECH library name that will be used for backend testing.</dd>
      <dt>Synthesis: </dt>
      <dd>Moved forward to support new flows presented in p1273_1.7.0.</dd>
      <dt>UPF Updates: </dt>
      <dd>port_idle_ff was added to the clamp files to be a 1 when power gated. This will prevent the fabric from waking up for no reason.</dd>
      <dd>port_idle_ff was added to prevent the asynchronous fifo from indicating non-idle conditions while powergated.</dd>
   </dl>

   <h2>Validation Updates:</h2>
   <p>Support for VCS v2013.06.4 added with PHASE2 BFM.</p>
   <p>Functional Coverage: 96%</p>
   <p>Line Coverage: 97%</p>]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
    <sip_speccon>
<![CDATA[
HTML
   <h2>Integration Notes:</h2>
   <p><b>NOTE:</b> CTECH_LIB_NAME must point to a valid synthesisable CTECH library when synthesising the IP.</p>
   <p><b>NOTE:</b> CTECH_LIB_NAME must point to a valid synthesisable/behavior CTECH library when simulating the IP.</p>
   <p>Migrated to Zircon 2013.3</p>]]>    </sip_speccon>
  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
    <sip_specin>
<![CDATA[
HTML
   <p>For support file an <b>HSD</b> at <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360">https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360</a></p>]]>    </sip_specin>
  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
