<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.3 November 19, 2012</version>
  <date>Sat Mar 23 18:21:17 PDT 2013</date>
  <user>jakrigel</user>
  <sip_name>47</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>0</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>0</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2013WW12</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>0</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>2013WW12</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jakrigel</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist>CSG_SIP_Proj_BellCreek@intel.com,CSG_SIP_Proj_Broxton@intel.com,CSG_SIP_Proj_Denverton@intel.com,CSG_SIP_Proj_SunrisePoint@intel.com,csg_sip_all@intel.com</sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed>4257648 4257843 4258286 4258602 4546896 4547265 4547372 4548437 4548554 4548563 4795624 4795627 4795775 4795859 4796650 4901939 4902214 4902223 4902436 4902555 4902556 4902871 56603 56628</sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>0</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<ol>
<li>Inserted DFx Secure Plugin inserted into Dynamo Wrapper.</li>
<li>Fabric Parameter added to insert asynchronous clock handshake and reset synchronizers for the entire fabric to support Chassis clocking and reset requirements.</li>
<li>Fabric Parameter added to insert the fabric PGCB to support Chassis power requirements.</li>
<li>Two parameters have been added to the corekit. They are PGCBEnabled and ChassisCompliantClocking. Both parameters default to 0 (i.e., no PGCB and legacy clocking). 
<ul>
<li>PGCBEnabled=0, ChassisCompliantClocking=0 – No PGCB, legacy clocking (default)</li>
<li>PGCBEnabled=0, ChassisCompliantClocking=1 – No PGCB, Chassis Compliant Clocking</li>
<li>PGCBEnabled=1, ChassisCompliantClocking=0 – INVALID CONFIGURATION</li>
<li>PGCBEnabled=0, ChassisCompliantClocking=1 – PGCB Enabled, Chassis Compliant Clocking</li>
</ul>
These parameters should be added to all *.params fabric spec files. It is required that all routers in a network have the same PGCBEnabled/ChassisCompliantClocking configuration.</li>
<li>Two parameters have been removed from the corekit. They are NOADestPref and RegSrcPref. These parameters must be removed from all *.params fabric spec files before assembling a network using the corekit in this release.</li>
<li>Resolved corner cases with POK asserting dynamically.</li>
<li>Integration Guide updated with latest list of interface pins. Descriptions will follow later.</li>
</ol>    ]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
    <sip_knissue>
<![CDATA[
HTML
<ol>
<li>Asynchronous to asynchronous port connections are not verifiable in this release. Support for this topological construct to be fixed in a future release.</li>
<li>The UPF files created by this release are syntactically correct. They compile in VCS-NLP and have been linted by Spyglass LP. However, they have not been verified via power aware simulation or in synthesis.</li>
<li>Spyglass LP reports several warnings and errors in the UPF files. These warnings and errors are understood and should be resolved by the next release. To the best of our knowledge, the power domains defined within the UPF accurately describe our intent.</li>
<li>CDC Violations on PGCB control signals to be cleaned in RTL 1.0.</li>
<li>LEC not supported in this version and will be running in RTL 1.0.</li>
<li>Integration guides are out of date.</li>
</ol>        ]]>    </sip_knissue>
  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
<![CDATA[Execute using the Dynamo command
- Please note that the Sideband Router cell map file needs to be updated per IP instance to replace generic library cells or risk getting behavior models.
]]>  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
