<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- Release file -->

<sip_release>
  <version>8.4 November 13, 2013</version>
  <date>Thu Jul 17 16:14:37 PDT 2014</date>
  <user>jakrigel</user>
  <sip_name>31</sip_name>
  <sip_variation>147</sip_variation>
  <sip_variation_id>147</sip_variation_id>
  <sip_reldate>2014WW29</sip_reldate>
  <sip_milestone>1p0</sip_milestone>
  <sip_relver>v4</sip_relver>
  <sip_relname>ALL_2014WW29_R1p0_v4</sip_relname>
  <sip_owner>jakrigel</sip_owner>
  <sip_dist></sip_dist>
  <sip_fixed></sip_fixed>
  <sip_open></sip_open>
  <sip_attachment>
  </sip_attachment>
  <sip_customers>
      <sip_customer>20</sip_customer>
  </sip_customers>
  <sip_base>927</sip_base>
  <sip_features>
    <sip_feature>
<![CDATA[
HTML
      <h2>RTL Updates:</h2>
      <dl>
         <dt>Micro-architecture Updates:</dt>
         <dd>
            Updated ENUM in sbetrgt to have a defined logic vector length. Was
            causing problems for specific version of Lintra.
         </dd>
         <dd>
            Updated clock request logic to use a more human readable and field
            tested asynchronous clock request module from the Sideband Fabric.
         </dd>

         <dt>PCRS: <dt>
         <dd>
            HSD <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=12041672">12041672</a>:
            Added an ingress outstanding completions counter which can be used
            for power management.
         </dd>
         <dt>HSDS: <dt>
         <dd>
            HSD <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=1202934316">1202934316</a>:
            agent_clk gate has a bug that it was blocking the clock before the
            agent_idle signal was able to cross over to the side_clk domain.
            This was causing the ISM to continually cycle between ACTIVE to
            IDLE to ACTIVE again.
         </dd>
         <dd>
            HSD <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#article?id=1202655458">1202655458</a>:
            Lintra was flagging unused ports in the endpoint when new feature
            was disabled.
         </dd>
      </dl>
      
      <h2>Backend Updates:</h2>
      <dl>
         <dt>CDC Updates: </dt>
         <dd>
            Removed support for *.v control files.
         </dd>
         <dd>
            Updated runCDC to use the TCL files used by runACECDC. This gives
            more complete coverage of possible endpoint configurations and is
            easier to maintain. When integrating the endpoint and leveraging
            the TCL files, modify the variables at the top of the files to
            match what was used during integration.
         </dd>
      </dl>]]>    </sip_feature>
  </sip_features>
  <sip_knissues>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_knissues>
  <sip_speccons>
<![CDATA[]]>  </sip_speccons>
  <sip_specins>
    <sip_specin>
<![CDATA[
HTML
      <ul>
         <li>For support file an <b>HSD</b> at <a href="https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360">https://hsdes.intel.com/home/default.html#magazine?id=101846185&contentId=1012194360</a></li>
         <li>Please note that Sideband Endpoint instantiations need to be uniquified in all IP's per the SEG POR instantiation and uniquification methodology to avoid module collisions with other instances of the endpoint with other IPs.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for handling current clock request logic</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for conditions of locally clock gating the agent_clk in asynchronous endpoints.</li>
         <li>Please read integration guide carefully for any necessary power gating logic that may be needed.</li>
      </ul>]]>    </sip_specin>
  </sip_specins>
  <sip_models>
      <sip_model>23</sip_model>
      <sip_model>4</sip_model>
  </sip_models>
</sip_release>
